Guide to the Firebrand Books records, 1984-2000.
Firebrand Books records,
- Series I. Author/Book Files
  - Parker & Hulme: Review Copies, 1995-2000 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Politics of the Heart: Pending, 1992-2000 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Politics of the Heart: Contracts, 1986-2000 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Von nun an nannten sie sich Mutter: by Uli Streib, ed., Orlanda Frauenverlag 1991 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Politics of the Heart: General, 1996-2000 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Politics of the Heart: General, 1992-1995 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Politics of the Heart: General, 1987-1991 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Politics of the Heart: General, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Politics of the Heart: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Politics of the Heart: A Lesbian Parenting Anthology by Sandra Pollack and Jeanne Vaughn, eds., Firebrand Books 1987 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Politics of the Heart: Reviews, 1987-1992 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Politics of the Heart: Review Copies, 1987-2000 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Post-Diagnosis: Pending, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Post-Diagnosis: Contracts, 1994-2000 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Post-Diagnosis: General, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Post-Diagnosis: General, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Post-Diagnosis: General, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Post-Diagnosis: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Post-Diagnosis: Poetry by Sandra Steingraber, Firebrand Books 1995 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Post-Diagnosis: Reviews, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Post-Diagnosis: Review Copies, 1994-2000 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Post-Dykes to Watch Out For: Pending, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Post-Dykes to Watch Out For: Contracts, 1998-2000 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Post-Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1998-2000 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Post-Dykes to Watch Out For: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Post-Dykes to Watch Out For: Cartoons by Alison Bechdel, Firebrand Books 2000 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Post-Dykes to Watch Out For: Reviews, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Post-Dykes to Watch Out For: Review Copies, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Presenting...Sister Noblues: Pending, 1988-1991 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Presenting...Sister Noblues: Contracts, 1987-2000 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Presenting...Sister Noblues: General, 1995-2000 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Presenting...Sister Noblues: General, 1989-1994 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Presenting...Sister Noblues: General, 1985-1988 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Presenting...Sister Noblues: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Presenting...Sister Noblues: Poetry by Hattie Gossett, Firebrand Books 1988 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Presenting...Sister Noblues: Reviews, 1988-1990 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Presenting...Sister Noblues: Review Copies, 1991-1997 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - The Price of Passion: Pending, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - The Price of Passion: Contracts, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - The Price of Passion: General, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - The Price of Passion: General, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - The Price of Passion: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - The Price of Passion: An Erotic Journey by Jess Wells, Firebrand Books 1999 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - The Price of Passion: Reviews, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - The Price of Passion: Review Copies, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Read My Lips: Pending, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Read My Lips: Contracts, 1997-2000 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Read My Lips: General, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Read My Lips: General, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Read My Lips: General, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Read My Lips: General, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Read My Lips: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Read My Lips: Sexual Subversion and the End of Gender by Riki Anne Wilchins, Firebrand Books 1997 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Read My Lips: Reviews, 1997-2000 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Read My Lips: Review Copies, 1997-2000 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Read My Lips: Review Copies, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Rebellion: Pending, 1991-1995 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Rebellion: Contracts, 1990-2000 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Rebellion: General, 1998-2000 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Rebellion: General, 1993-1997 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Rebellion: General, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Rebellion: General, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Rebellion: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Rebellion: Essays 1980-1991 by Minnie Bruce Pratt, Firebrand Books 1991 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Rebellion: Reviews, 1991-1993 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Rebellion: Review Copies, 1991-2000 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Restoring the Color of Roses: Pending, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Restoring the Color of Roses: Contracts, 1992-2000 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Restoring the Color of Roses: General, 1992-2000 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Restoring the Color of Roses: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Restoring the Color of Roses: tape cassette "This way Out" Interview of Barrie Borich by Michelle Johnson August 1993, tr-11674 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Restoring the Color of Roses: by Barrie Jean Borich, Firebrand Books 1993 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Restoring the Color of Roses: Reviews, 1993-1995 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Restoring the Color of Roses: Review Copies, 1993-1997 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - A Restricted Country: Pending, 1987-1996 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - A Restricted Country: Contracts, 1986-2000 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - A Restricted Country: (British Edition) by Joan Nestle, Sheba Feminist Publishers 1987, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - A Restricted Country: (2nd British Edition) by Joan Nestle, Pandora 1987, 1988, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - A Restricted Country: video cassette "Straight for the Money" by Hima B., Himaphiliac Productions 1994, V-9864 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - A Restricted Country: General, 1999-2001 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - A Restricted Country: General, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - A Restricted Country: General, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - A Restricted Country: General, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - A Restricted Country: General, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - A Restricted Country: General, 1989-1991 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - A Restricted Country: General, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - A Restricted Country: General, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - A Restricted Country: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - A Restricted Country: by Joan Nestle, Firebrand Books 1987 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - A Restricted Country: Reviews, 1987-1996 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - A Restricted Country: Review Copies, 1987-1997 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - The Rooms We Make Our Own: Pending, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - The Rooms We Make Our Own: Contracts, 1995-2000 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - The Rooms We Make Our Own: General, 1994-2000 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - The Rooms We Make Our Own: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - The Rooms We Make Our Own: by Toni Mirosevich, Firebrand Books 1996 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - The Rooms We Make Our Own: Reviews, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - The Rooms We Make Our Own: Review Copies, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Running Fiercely Toward a High Thin Sound: Pending, 1992-1997 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Running Fiercely Toward a High Thin Sound: Contracts, 1991-2000 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Running Fiercely Toward a High Thin Sound: General, 1995-2000 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Running Fiercely Toward a High Thin Sound: General, 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Running Fiercely Toward a High Thin Sound: General, 1986-1992 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Running Fiercely Toward a High Thin Sound: Promo Materials (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Running Fiercely Toward a High Thin Sound: A Novel by Judith Katz, Firebrand Books 1992 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Running Fiercely Toward a High Thin Sound: Reviews, 1992-1997 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Running Fiercely Toward a High Thin Sound: Review Copies, 1992-1998 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Sacred Space: Pending, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Sacred Space: Contracts, 1988-2000 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Sacred Space: General, 1988-2000 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Sacred Space: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Sacred Space: A Feminist Vision of Astrology by Geraldine Hatch Hanon, Firebrand Books 1990 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Sacred Space: Reviews, 1990-1996 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Sacred Space: Review Copies, 1990-1998 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Sanctuary: Pending, 1986-1991 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Sanctuary: Contracts, 1985-2000 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Sanctuary: General, 1990-2000 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Sanctuary: General, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Sanctuary: General, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Sanctuary: General, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Sanctuary: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Sanctuary: A Journey by Judith McDaniel, Firebrand Books 1987 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Sanctuary: Reviews, 1987-1996 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Sanctuary: Review Copies, 1987-1998 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Sans Souci: Pending, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Sans Souci: Contracts, 1989-2000 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Sans Souci: (Canadian Edition) by Dionne Brand, Williams-Wallace Publishers 1988 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Sans Souci: General, 1994-2000 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Sans Souci: General, 1988-1993 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Sans Souci: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Sans Souci: and Other Stories by Dionne Brand, Firebrand Books 1988, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Sans Souci: Reviews, 1989-1996 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Sans Souci: Review Copies, 1989-1998 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Scuttlebutt: Pending, 1990-1997 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Scuttlebutt: Contracts, 1989-2000 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Scuttlebutt: A Novel (Canadian Edition) by Jana L. Williams, Press Gang Publishers 1990 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Scuttlebutt: General, 1988-2000 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Scuttlebutt: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Scuttlebutt: A Novel by Jana Williams, Firebrand Books 1990 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Scuttlebutt: Reviews, 1990-1994 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Scuttlebutt: Review Copies, 1990-2000 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - The Second Coming of Curly Red: Pending, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - The Second Coming of Curly Red: Contracts, 1998-2000 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - The Second Coming of Curly Red: General, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - The Second Coming of Curly Red: General, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - The Second Coming of Curly Red: Promo Materials (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - The Second Coming of Curly Red: A Novel by Jody Seay, Firebrand Books 1999 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - The Second Coming of Curly Red: Reviews, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - The Second Coming of Curly Red: Review Copies, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - S/he: Pending, 1994-1996 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - S/he: Contracts, 1994-2000 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - S/he: Tape Cassette-Leslie Feinberg & Minnie Bruce Pratt, OutWrite 1993, tr-11675 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - S/he: General, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - S/he: General, 1998-1999 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - S/he: General, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - S/he: General, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - S/he: General, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - S/he: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - S/he: by Minnie Bruce Pratt, Firebrand Books 1995 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - S/he: Reviews, 1995-1998 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - S/he: Review Copies, 1994-1999 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Shoulders: Pending, 1986-1993 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Shoulders: Contracts, 1986-2000 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Shoulders: General, 1989-2000 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Shoulders: General, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Shoulders: General, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Shoulders: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Shoulders: A Novel by Georgia Cotrell, Firebrand Books 1987 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Shoulders: Reviews, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Shoulders: Review Copies, 1987-1997 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Simple Songs: Pending, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Simple Songs: Contracts, 1988-2000 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Simple Songs: General, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Simple Songs: General, 1994-1998 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Simple Songs: General, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Simple Songs: General, 1988-1991 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Simple Songs: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Simple Songs: Stories by Vickie Sears, Firebrand Books 1990 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Simple Songs: Reviews, 1990-1995 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Simple Songs: Review Copies, 1990-1996 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Sister Safety Pin: Pending, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Sister Safety Pin: Contracts, 1993-2000 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Sister Safety Pin: General, 1990-2000 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Sister Safety Pin: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Sister Safety Pin: Reviews, 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Sister safety Pin: Review Copies, 1994-2000 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Skin: Pending, 1993-1997 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Skin: Contracts, 1990-2000 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Skin: Rights, 1993-2001 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Skin: (British Edition) by Dorothy Allison, Pandora 1994, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Peau: (Skin-French Edition) by Dorothy Allison, Éditions Balland 1994, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Huid: (Skin-Dutch Edition) by Dorothy Allison, Uitgeverij Atlas 1994, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Skin: General, 2000-2001 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Skin: General, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Skin: General, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Skin: General, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Skin: General, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Skin: General, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Skin: General, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Skin: General, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Skin: General, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Skin: General, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Skin: General, 1990-1993 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Skin: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Skin: Cassette Tapes- American Bookseller Association Sunday Book and Author Breakfast 1995, OutWrite '95 Conversation III (Dorothy Allison & Bertha Harris), tr-11676-11677 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Skin: Talking About Sex, Class & Literature ny Dorothy Allison, Firebrand Books 1994 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Skin: Reviews, 1994-2000 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Skin: Review Copies, 1994-2000 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Skin: Review Copies, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Spawn of Dykes to Watch Out For: Pending, 1993-2000 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Spawn of Dykes to Watch Out For: Contracts, 1992-2000 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Le Mome des Lesbiennes a suivre: (Spawn of Dykes to Watch Out For-French Edition) by Alison Bechdel, Cyprine 1993, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Spawn of Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1998-2000 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Spawn of Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1994-1997 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Spawn of Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Spawn of Dykes to Watch Out For: General, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Spawn of Dykes to Watch Out For: by Alison Bechdel, Firebrand Books 1993 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Spawn of Dykes to Watch Out For: Reviews, 1993-2000 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Spawn of Dykes to Watch Out For: Review Copies, 1993-2000 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Speaking Dreams: Pending, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Speaking Dreams: Contracts, 1991-1996 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Speaking Dreams: General, 1990-1998 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Speaking Dreams: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Speaking Dreams: by Severna Park, firebrand Books 1992 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Speaking Dreams: Reviews, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Speaking Dreams: Review Copies, 1992-1995 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Split-level Dykes to Watch Out For: Pending, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Split-level Dykes to Watch Out For: Contracts, 1997-2000 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Split-level Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Split-level Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Split-level Dykes to Watch Out For: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Split-level Dykes to Watch Out For: by Alison Bechdel, Firebrand Books 1998 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Split-level Dykes to Watch Out For: Reviews, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Split-level Dykes to Watch Out For: Review Copies, 1998-2000 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Stardust Bound: Pending, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Stardust Bound: Contracts, 1993-2000 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Stardust Bound: General, 1993-2000 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Stardust Bound: Promo Materials (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Stardust Bound: A Novel by Karen Cadora, Firebrand Books 1994 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Stardust Bound: Reviews, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Stardust Bound: Review Copies, 1994-1998 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Staying the Distance: Pending, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Staying the Distance: Contracts, 1993-2000 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Staying the Distance: General, 1993-2000 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Staying the Distance: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Staying the Distance: A Novel by Franci McMahon, Firebrand Books 1994 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Staying the Distance: Reviews, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Staying the Distance: Review Copies, 1994-1999 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Stone Butch Blues: Pending, 1992-2000 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Stone Butch Blues: Contracts, 1992-2000 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Stone Butch Blues: Contracts (Rights), 1990-2000 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Traume in den erwachenden Morgen: (Stone Butch Blues-German Edition) by Leslie Feinberg, Krug & Schadenberg 1993, 1996 and Een butch zingt de blues: (Stone Butch Blues-Dutch Edition) by Leslie Feinberg, Schorer 1993, 1995, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Stone Butch Blues: Slovenian and Chinese Editions 2000 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Stone Butch Blues: by Leslie Feinberg, Quality Paperback Book Club 1993, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Stone Butch Blues: General, 2000-2001 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Stone Butch Blues: General, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Stone Butch Blues: General, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Stone Butch Blues: General, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Stone Butch Blues: General, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Stone Butch Blues: General, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Stone Butch Blues: General, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Stone Butch Blues: General, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Stone Butch Blues: General, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Stone Butch Blues: General, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Stone Butch Blues: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Stone Butch Blues: A Novel by Leslie Feinberg, Firebrand Books 1993 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Stone Butch Blues: Reviews, 1992-1999 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Stone Butch Blues: Review Copies, 1993-1999 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - The Sun Is Not Merciful: Pending, 1985-1993 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - The Sun Is Not Merciful: Contracts, 1984-2000 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - The Sun Is Not Merciful: General, 1995-2000 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - The Sun Is Not Merciful: General, 1992-1994 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - The Sun Is Not Merciful: General, 1988-1991 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - The Sun Is Not Merciful: General, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - The Sun Is Not Merciful: General, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - The Sun Is Not Merciful: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - The Sun Is Not Merciful: Short Stories by Anna Lee Walters, Firebrand Books 1985 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - The Sun Is Not Merciful: Reviews, 1985-1988 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - The Sun Is Not Merciful: Review Copies, 1985-1999 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Talking Indian: Pending, 1992-1996 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Talking Indian: Contracts, 1990-2000 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Talking Indian: General, 1997-2000 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Talking Indian: General, 1993-1996 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Talking Indian: General, 1989-1992 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Talking Indian: Promo Materials (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Talking Indian: Reflections on Survival and Writing by Anna Lee Walters, Firebrand Books 1992 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Talking Indian: Reviews, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Talking Indian: Review Copies, 1992-2000 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Tender Warriors: Pending, 1986-1990 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Tender Warriors: Contracts, 1985-2000 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Tender Warriors: General, 1987-2000 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Tender Warriors: General, 1984-1986 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Tender Warriors: Promo Materials (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Tender Warriors: A Novel by Rachel Guido DeVries, Firebrand Books 1986 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Tender Warriors: Reviews, 1986-1994 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Tender Warriors: Review Copies, 1986-1997 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - This Is About Incest: Pending, 1986-1991 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - This Is about Incest: Contracts, 1986-2000 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - This Is About Incest: General, 1993-2000 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - This Is About Incest: General, 1989-1992 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - This Is About Incest: General, 1985-1988 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - This Is About Incest: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - This Is About Incest: by Margaret Randall, Firebrand Books 1987 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - This Is About Incest: Reviews, 1987-1996 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - This Is About Incest: Review Copies, 1987-1999 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - This Is What Lesbian Looks Like: Pending, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - This Is What Lesbian Looks Like: Contracts, 1998-2000 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - This Is What Lesbian Looks Like: General, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - This Is What Lesbian Looks Like: General, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - This Is What Lesbian Looks Like: General, 1997-1999 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - This Is What Lesbian Looks Like: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - This Is What Lesbian Looks Like: Dyke activists Take on the 21st Century by Kris Kleindienst, ed., Firebrand Books 1999 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - This Is What Lesbian Looks Like: Reviews 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - This Is What Lesbian Looks Like: Review Copies, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - The Threshing Floor: Pending, 1987-2000 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - The Threshing Floor: Contracts, 1987-2000 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - The Threshing Floor: (British Edition) by Barbara Burford, Sheba Feminist Publishers 1986 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - A Dangerous Knowing: Four Black Women Poets, Sheba Feminist Publishers (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - The Threshing Floor: General, 1989-2000 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - The Threshing Floor: General, 1985-1988 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - The Threshing Floor: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - The Threshing Floor: Short Stories by Barbara Burford, Firebrand Books 1986, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - The Threshing Floor: Reviews, 1987-1989 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - The Threshing Floor: Review Copies, 1987-1998 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - To Be Continued...: Pending, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - To Be Continued...: Contracts, 1997-2000 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - To Be Continued...: General, 1998-2000 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - To Be Continued...: General, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - To Be Continued...: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - To Be Continued...: by Michele Karlsberg & Karen X. Tulchinsky, Firebrand Books 1998 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - To Be Continued...: Reviews, 1998-2001 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - To Be Continued...: Review Copies, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - To Be Continued: Take Two: Pending, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - To Be Continued: Take Two: Contracts, 1998-2000 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - To Be Continued: Take Two: General, 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - To Be Continued: Take Two: General, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - To Be Continued: Take Two: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - To Be Continued: Take Two: by Michele Karlsberg and Karen X. Tulchinsky, eds., Firebrand Books 1999 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - To Be Continued: Take Two: Reviews, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - To Be Continued: Take Two: Review Copies, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Too Queer: Pending, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Too Queer: Contracts, 1994-2000 (Box 28, Folder 7)